Aram Zhamkochyan

26-05-1990 +374 (41) 32 52 53 aramzham@hotmail.com

Objective: Developer

Summary

Over past several years my career has evolved from Call Center operator to C# developer. I got acquainted with IT technologies and with programming in Microsoft Armenia. After finishing the internship, at present I'm a .Net software engineer at BetConstruct. As an active team player, I'm always open to learn and to share knowledge. I hope that my sense of responsibility, hardworking and my ability to find solutions to different situations will be useful in my future projects.

Technical skills

- **Languages:** C# 6.0, Python 3 and JavaScript (basics)
- Libraries and Frameworks: Object Oriented Programming, .NET Framework 4.6, LINQ, Win Forms, WPF, WCF, Web Api, NT Services
- Database: T-SQL, Entity Framework, ADO.Net
- Web technologies: HTML, CSS (basics), Parsing
- VSC: GitHub
- **IDE:** Visual Studio 2015, 2017

Work Experience		
07.2017 - present	.Net software engineer - BetConstruct	
12.2012 - 06.2014	POS-terminal service division specialist - «Unibank» CJSC	
07.2012 - 12.2012	Processing Center specialist – «Unibank» CJSC	
05.2009 -05.2010	Call Center operator – «Armenian Card» CJSC	
Education		
2015 - 2016 2012 - 2014	University of Poitiers (France) – Master 1, Finance de marché Yerevan State University, Faculty of Economy – Master's degree	

2015 - 2016	University of Poitiers (France) – Master 1, Finance de marché
2012 - 2014	Yerevan State University, Faculty of Economy – Master's degree
2010 - 2012	Military Service
2006 - 2010	Yerevan State University, Faculty of Economy – Bachelor's degree
2001 - 2006	Anania Shirakatsi Lycee
1996 - 2001	Levon Shant N4 elementary school

Language skills

- Armenian mother language
- Russian fluent
- English good (TOEIC 890/990)
- French good (B2 level)